import "Catalog/catalog.css";


// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],

}



export var cards = {

  //#region Table de 11
  "11x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "11x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "11"
  },
  "11x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "22"
  },
  "11x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "33"
  },
  "11x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "44"
  },
  "11x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "55"
  },
  "11x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "66"
  },
  "11x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "77"
  },
  "11x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "88"
  },
  "11x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "99"
  },
  "11x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '11 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "110"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 11

  //#region Table de 12
  "12x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "12x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "12x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "24"
  },
  "12x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "36"
  },
  "12x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "48"
  },
  "12x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "60"
  },
  "12x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "72"
  },
  "12x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "84"
  },
  "12x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "96"
  },
  "12x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "108"
  },
  "12x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '12 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "120"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 12

  //#region Table de 13
  "13x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "13x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "13"
  },
  "13x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "26"
  },
  "13x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "39"
  },
  "13x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "52"
  },
  "13x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "65"
  },
  "13x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "78"
  },
  "13x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "91"
  },
  "13x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "104"
  },
  "13x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "117"
  },
  "13x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '13 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "130"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 13

  //#region Table de 14
  "14x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "14x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "14x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "28"
  },
  "14x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "42"
  },
  "14x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "56"
  },
  "14x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "70"
  },
  "14x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "84"
  },
  "14x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "98"
  },
  "14x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "112"
  },
  "14x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "126"
  },
  "14x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '14 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "140"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 14

  //#region Table de 15
  "15x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "15x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "15x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "30"
  },
  "15x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "45"
  },
  "15x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "60"
  },
  "15x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "75"
  },
  "15x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "90"
  },
  "15x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "105"
  },
  "15x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "120"
  },
  "15x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "135"
  },
  "15x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '15 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "150"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 15


};